Can't you come in and have tea now, Peter?
Peter,你不能现在进来喝茶吗?
Not yet.
还不能.
I must water the garden first.
我得先给花园浇水.
Do you have to water it now?
你一定得现在浇吗?
I'm afraid I must.
恐怕我得现在浇.
Look at it!
你看看它,
It's terribly dry.
干得厉害.
What a nuisance!
真是个麻烦事!
Last summer it was very dry, too.
去年夏天它也是干得很.
Don't you remember?
你不记得了吗?
I had to water it every day.
我不得不每天浇水.
Well, I'll have tea by myself.
好吧,我一个人喝茶了.
That was quick!
好快啊!
Have you finished already?
你已经浇完了?
Yes. Look out of the window.
是的.你看看窗外.
It's raining!
下雨了!
That means You don't need to water the garden.
那就是说,你不必给花园浇水了.
That was a pleasant surprise.
那是个令人愉快的惊喜.
It means I can have tea, instead.
这意味着我可以喝茶了.